



Matteo Massetti

Nationality: Italian Date of birth: 16/12/1997

Phone number: (+39) 3771144748

Email address: matteomassetti8@gmail.com

Website: https://matteomass.github.io/

• Home: Via Mafalada di Savoia 18/c, 06083 Bastia Umbra (Italy)

ABOUT ME

I'm a Software Engineer with a specific field in the field of Artificial Intelligence. My knowledge is not limited to this area but ranges in different areas of programming, such as blockchain and mobile programming. In almost two years of work experience I have gained and honed the skills needed to work effectively in teams.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software developer

Micra s.r.l. [04/07/2021 - Current]

City: Corciano Country: Italy

Full Stack Developer of products, services and platforms in banking and industry. Researcher in the field of Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence.

Internship

Università degli studi di Perugia [30/09/2018 – 30/12/2018]

Develop of a plug-in for the Moodle platform, which could facilitate and automate the administration and correction of multiple-choice questionnaires in order to test the knowledge of a large group of university students efficiently.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Master's Degree in Computer Science - Curriculum Artificial Intelligence

Università di Pisa [30/09/2019 - Current]

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Università degli Studi di Perugia [19/09/2016 – 19/09/2019]

Final grade: 110/100 con Lode

Thesis: Multidimensional Link Prediction

Administration, Finance and Marketing Diploma

Istituto R. Bonghi, Assisi [09/09/2011 – 09/06/2016]

Final grade: 98/100

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Italiano

Other language(s):

Inglese

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python / Latex / C, C++ / Java / HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS, PHP / SQL / Solidity

Development Tools

Github, git / Visula Studio Code / Python Anaconda Environmnet / Remix IDE / Eclipse IDE / Piattaforma Remix - Ethereum / Android Studio (sviluppo mobile Android) / Overleaf

Programming Skills

Machine learning / Blockchain e Smart Contract / Big Data Analysis / sviluppo sistema IoT

Certificates

Expert.ai ROOKIE certification / Expert.ai PRO certification

NETWORKS AND MEMBERSHIPS

Mensa Italia

[28/04/2022 - Current]

Mensa is an international no-profit organization open to people who score at the 98th percentile or higher on a standardised, supervised IQ test.

The association has 3 goals:

- 1. Discover and encourage human intelligence for the benefit of human beings.
- 2. Encourage research into the nature, characteristics and uses of intelligence
- 3. Encourage social contacts among Members by means of conferences, discussions, publications, study groups, conventions or other means useful for these purposes